[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 3, "question": "Are you under the influence of any substances?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "under", "the", "influence", "of", "any", "substances", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 4, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["P.T. Barnum"]}, "docId": "110309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 32, "question": "When you watch what's happening with Charlie right now, what are you thinking?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "watch", "what", "'s", "happening", "with", "Charlie", "right", "now", ",", "what", "are", "you", "thinking", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 33, "answer": "P.T. Barnum.", "answer_tokens": ["P.T.", "Barnum", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "RB", "CC", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "EX", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 40, "question": "Do you accept any of that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "accept", "any", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 41, "answer": "I think maybe the whole machete thing might have been something that he's running and gunning with right now but certainly the home tape that he did the night before, I fully recognized and I heard a clip that you had, I think it was Todd Bridges who made the comment of, yes, I've been there, I know that -- I know that guy.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "maybe", "the", "whole", "machete", "thing", "might", "have", "been", "something", "that", "he", "'s", "running", "and", "gunning", "with", "right", "now", "but", "certainly", "the", "home", "tape", "that", "he", "did", "the", "night", "before", ",", "I", "fully", "recognized", "and", "I", "heard", "a", "clip", "that", "you", "had", ",", "I", "think", "it", "was", "Todd", "Bridges", "who", "made", "the", "comment", "of", ",", "yes", ",", "I", "'ve", "been", "there", ",", "I", "know", "that", "--", "I", "know", "that", "guy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "I mean are you seriously worried that Charlie Sheen is slowly killing himself here?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "are", "you", "seriously", "worried", "that", "Charlie", "Sheen", "is", "slowly", "killing", "himself", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "Yes, I don't even think it's slowly right now.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "even", "think", "it", "'s", "slowly", "right", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie Sheen"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ":"], "qSentId": 88, "question": "I mean the man has an anger issue, a rage issue, and I think the more that people like you who have this incredible platform to come from who are -- I don't want to use the word enabling but who are sort of egging him on, tickling that little funny bone that says, yes, yes, this is -- hey, I've got, you know, Aunt Donna's DNA and I feel like people love to watch a circus, right?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "the", "man", "has", "an", "anger", "issue", ",", "a", "rage", "issue", ",", "and", "I", "think", "the", "more", "that", "people", "like", "you", "who", "have", "this", "incredible", "platform", "to", "come", "from", "who", "are", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "use", "the", "word", "enabling", "but", "who", "are", "sort", "of", "egging", "him", "on", ",", "tickling", "that", "little", "funny", "bone", "that", "says", ",", "yes", ",", "yes", ",", "this", "is", "--", "hey", ",", "I", "'ve", "got", ",", "you", "know", ",", "Aunt", "Donna", "'s", "DNA", "and", "I", "feel", "like", "people", "love", "to", "watch", "a", "circus", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RBR", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "WP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "CC", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", ",", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", ",", "NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "DT", "VBZ", ":", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 89, "answer": "I mean I'm told --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", "I", "'m", "told", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Donna"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 122, "question": "I mean when you hear him talk like that, what are you seeing, the classic signs of an addict in your view?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "when", "you", "hear", "him", "talk", "like", "that", ",", "what", "are", "you", "seeing", ",", "the", "classic", "signs", "of", "an", "addict", "in", "your", "view", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 123, "answer": "Oh, without question.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "without", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 149, "question": "And being the face of CBS which is, you know, supposed to be a family, you know, network and the families out there, and he's working with a 9 or 10 or 11-year-old boy, so he comes into the set, he's off a crack run, he's been with a few hookers the night before, what do you think he's talking about with an 11-year-old?", "question_tokens": ["And", "being", "the", "face", "of", "CBS", "which", "is", ",", "you", "know", ",", "supposed", "to", "be", "a", "family", ",", "you", "know", ",", "network", "and", "the", "families", "out", "there", ",", "and", "he", "'s", "working", "with", "a", "9", "or", "10", "or", "11-year-old", "boy", ",", "so", "he", "comes", "into", "the", "set", ",", "he", "'s", "off", "a", "crack", "run", ",", "he", "'s", "been", "with", "a", "few", "hookers", "the", "night", "before", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "he", "'s", "talking", "about", "with", "an", "11-year-old", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "WDT", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "CD", "CC", "CD", "CC", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "DT", "NN", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 150, "answer": "Well, look, he --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "look", ",", "he", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CBS"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 185, "question": "What was it that finally snapped you back into normal life again?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "it", "that", "finally", "snapped", "you", "back", "into", "normal", "life", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 186, "answer": "I don't think I had ever been afraid of the drug itself before.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "I", "had", "ever", "been", "afraid", "of", "the", "drug", "itself", "before", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 192, "question": "And Mackenzie, for you, was it -- Mackenzie, for you, was it getting fired from the show that finally woke you up?", "question_tokens": ["And", "Mackenzie", ",", "for", "you", ",", "was", "it", "--", "Mackenzie", ",", "for", "you", ",", "was", "it", "getting", "fired", "from", "the", "show", "that", "finally", "woke", "you", "up", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 193, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mackenzie", "Mackenzie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 209, "question": "Or does he have to save himself?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "does", "he", "have", "to", "save", "himself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 210, "answer": "I think it's got to be a combination of both.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "got", "to", "be", "a", "combination", "of", "both", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 234, "question": "I mean if Charlie used to go down this road how difficult is it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "if", "Charlie", "used", "to", "go", "down", "this", "road", "how", "difficult", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 235, "answer": "It won't be easy for him as the doctor just mentioned.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "wo", "n't", "be", "easy", "for", "him", "as", "the", "doctor", "just", "mentioned", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 248, "question": "Am I right, Dr. Samuels?", "question_tokens": ["Am", "I", "right", ",", "Dr.", "Samuels", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 249, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dr. Samuels"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "Do you think he really has any concept of what's going on here?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "he", "really", "has", "any", "concept", "of", "what", "'s", "going", "on", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "To be honest with you I couldn't answer that question.", "answer_tokens": ["To", "be", "honest", "with", "you", "I", "could", "n't", "answer", "that", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 301, "question": "What kind of people were your parents?", "question_tokens": ["What", "kind", "of", "people", "were", "your", "parents", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 302, "answer": "They were very nice people.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "were", "very", "nice", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 310, "question": "Was there any stress or trouble that you could look at and say well, maybe we should have seen warning signs here?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "there", "any", "stress", "or", "trouble", "that", "you", "could", "look", "at", "and", "say", "well", ",", "maybe", "we", "should", "have", "seen", "warning", "signs", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "CC", "VB", "RB", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBG", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "Absolutely none.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "none", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 315, "question": "When did you hear what had happened?", "question_tokens": ["When", "did", "you", "hear", "what", "had", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 316, "answer": "Probably 20 minutes after it had happened.", "answer_tokens": ["Probably", "20", "minutes", "after", "it", "had", "happened", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 322, "question": "What-- how do you possibly come to terms with it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "--", "how", "do", "you", "possibly", "come", "to", "terms", "with", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "It is just absolute disbelief.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "just", "absolute", "disbelief", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 327, "question": "Do you know where he got the guns?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "where", "he", "got", "the", "guns", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 328, "answer": "No idea.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "idea", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last week"]}, "docId": "110309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VB", "NN", "IN", "CD", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "I mean, what do you think will happen next for this family?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "will", "happen", "next", "for", "this", "family", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "You know, we will just continue to pull together like we had this last week and take care of one another.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "we", "will", "just", "continue", "to", "pull", "together", "like", "we", "had", "this", "last", "week", "and", "take", "care", "of", "one", "another", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 340, "question": "Did you get any kind of inkling that something like this could ever happen?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "get", "any", "kind", "of", "inkling", "that", "something", "like", "this", "could", "ever", "happen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 341, "answer": "No, I never saw anything like this.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "never", "saw", "anything", "like", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 350, "question": "Do you think that is the correct way this should proceed?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "that", "is", "the", "correct", "way", "this", "should", "proceed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "DT", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 351, "answer": "That's a hard question for me to answer.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "a", "hard", "question", "for", "me", "to", "answer", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 360, "question": "What can you possibly say to them?", "question_tokens": ["What", "can", "you", "possibly", "say", "to", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 361, "answer": "Man, I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["Man", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NPR", "NPR"]}, "docId": "110309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 400, "question": "Was she right to go?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "she", "right", "to", "go", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 401, "answer": "Well, first, let me explain that as the ombudsman of NPR, I am not representing NPR.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", ",", "let", "me", "explain", "that", "as", "the", "ombudsman", "of", "NPR", ",", "I", "am", "not", "representing", "NPR", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Vivian Schiller"]}, "docId": "110309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "EX", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ":", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NNP", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "CC", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 411, "question": "Can you be responsible if you are chief executive of such a huge organization for everything that everybody in it does and says?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "be", "responsible", "if", "you", "are", "chief", "executive", "of", "such", "a", "huge", "organization", "for", "everything", "that", "everybody", "in", "it", "does", "and", "says", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "CC", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "Well, as I understand, the board basically decided that there have been too many things that have happened recently that would make it -- that hindered Vivian Schiller from actually going ahead and doing her job.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "as", "I", "understand", ",", "the", "board", "basically", "decided", "that", "there", "have", "been", "too", "many", "things", "that", "have", "happened", "recently", "that", "would", "make", "it", "--", "that", "hindered", "Vivian", "Schiller", "from", "actually", "going", "ahead", "and", "doing", "her", "job", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 417, "question": "Would it be easier if the NPR simply wasn't funded by the government?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "it", "be", "easier", "if", "the", "NPR", "simply", "was", "n't", "funded", "by", "the", "government", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "Well, certainly not right off the bat.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "certainly", "not", "right", "off", "the", "bat", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NPR"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "Is this kind of stunt fair game, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "kind", "of", "stunt", "fair", "game", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "Well, of course, it's fair game.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "of", "course", ",", "it", "'s", "fair", "game", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "CC", "DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "This guy wouldn't have said this stuff if he knew he was being recorded, would he?", "question_tokens": ["This", "guy", "would", "n't", "have", "said", "this", "stuff", "if", "he", "knew", "he", "was", "being", "recorded", ",", "would", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "VBN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "No, but this is done all the time.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "but", "this", "is", "done", "all", "the", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Geraldo Rivera", "Geraldo Rivera"]}, "docId": "110309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJR", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ":", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 454, "question": "Well, you are, really, aren't you?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "are", ",", "really", ",", "are", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 455, "answer": "No more so than Geraldo Rivera -- than Geraldo Rivera is.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "more", "so", "than", "Geraldo", "Rivera", "--", "than", "Geraldo", "Rivera", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["James O'Keefe"]}, "docId": "110309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 467, "question": "Where do you draw the line?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "do", "you", "draw", "the", "line", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 468, "answer": "If James O'Keefe, who is an independent journalist, comes to me with something that doesn't sit right with me, I'm going to pass on it.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "James", "O'Keefe", ",", "who", "is", "an", "independent", "journalist", ",", "comes", "to", "me", "with", "something", "that", "does", "n't", "sit", "right", "with", "me", ",", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "pass", "on", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 476, "question": "How do you ensure that somebody else isn't right now getting stitched up?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "ensure", "that", "somebody", "else", "is", "n't", "right", "now", "getting", "stitched", "up", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "VBN", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 477, "answer": "Well, I think that it's a cautionary tale, that this is a new world we live in.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "that", "it", "'s", "a", "cautionary", "tale", ",", "that", "this", "is", "a", "new", "world", "we", "live", "in", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NPR"]}, "docId": "110309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", ":", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 485, "question": "Andrew?", "question_tokens": ["Andrew", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 486, "answer": "Well, first of all, I will say this: the best coverage on this incident has been NPR.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "I", "will", "say", "this", ":", "the", "best", "coverage", "on", "this", "incident", "has", "been", "NPR", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 494, "question": "They're not all choir boys, are they?", "question_tokens": ["They", "'re", "not", "all", "choir", "boys", ",", "are", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 495, "answer": "I could accept that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "could", "accept", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "CD", "NN", ",", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "How did you manage to avoid the terrible fate that befell your colleagues?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "manage", "to", "avoid", "the", "terrible", "fate", "that", "befell", "your", "colleagues", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "NN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "Because I woke up one day, 27 years old -- I remember it was my last court appearance.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "I", "woke", "up", "one", "day", ",", "27", "years", "old", "--", "I", "remember", "it", "was", "my", "last", "court", "appearance", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 572, "question": "What was rock bottom?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "rock", "bottom", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 573, "answer": "Rock bottom for me was one day I was at a motel.", "answer_tokens": ["Rock", "bottom", "for", "me", "was", "one", "day", "I", "was", "at", "a", "motel", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Lake San Antonio"]}, "docId": "110309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 591, "question": "When did you hear that Gary had died?", "question_tokens": ["When", "did", "you", "hear", "that", "Gary", "had", "died", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 592, "answer": "I was actually out at Lake San Antonio on my jet skis.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "actually", "out", "at", "Lake", "San", "Antonio", "on", "my", "jet", "skis", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gary"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 615, "question": "Right?", "question_tokens": ["Right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 616, "answer": "That's exactly right.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "exactly", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 631, "question": "Arnold, ain't I your big brother who loves you, who worries about you?", "question_tokens": ["Arnold", ",", "ai", "n't", "I", "your", "big", "brother", "who", "loves", "you", ",", "who", "worries", "about", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "NNS", "PRP", ",", "WP", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 632, "answer": "And takes care of you, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "takes", "care", "of", "you", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 635, "question": "Todd, when you see what's happened to Charlie Sheen, what goes through your mind?", "question_tokens": ["Todd", ",", "when", "you", "see", "what", "'s", "happened", "to", "Charlie", "Sheen", ",", "what", "goes", "through", "your", "mind", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "POS", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 636, "answer": "Well, for me, I know that addiction is very powerful.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "for", "me", ",", "I", "know", "that", "addiction", "is", "very", "powerful", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie Sheen"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 646, "question": "Why do people do that?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "people", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "NNS", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 647, "answer": "Because for me, I think what I was going through -- I call it cocaine psychosis.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "for", "me", ",", "I", "think", "what", "I", "was", "going", "through", "--", "I", "call", "it", "cocaine", "psychosis", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", ":", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", ":", "EX", "VBZ", "CD", "NNS", "WDT", "MD", "VB", ",", "NN", "RP", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 657, "question": "Do you worry what will happen to Charlie if he doesn't get help?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "worry", "what", "will", "happen", "to", "Charlie", "if", "he", "does", "n't", "get", "help", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 658, "answer": "Yeah, everyone -- anybody who is in addiction, you know what -- there's three things that can happen, end up mentally crazy the rest of your life, in prison the rest of your life or you're going to die.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "everyone", "--", "anybody", "who", "is", "in", "addiction", ",", "you", "know", "what", "--", "there", "'s", "three", "things", "that", "can", "happen", ",", "end", "up", "mentally", "crazy", "the", "rest", "of", "your", "life", ",", "in", "prison", "the", "rest", "of", "your", "life", "or", "you", "'re", "going", "to", "die", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 661, "question": "Have you met Charlie Sheen?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "met", "Charlie", "Sheen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 662, "answer": "I know him.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "know", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie Sheen"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 679, "question": "If you got a chance to talk to him, what would you say to him?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "got", "a", "chance", "to", "talk", "to", "him", ",", "what", "would", "you", "say", "to", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 680, "answer": "A lot of things, but I would try to figure out the core of his problem.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "lot", "of", "things", ",", "but", "I", "would", "try", "to", "figure", "out", "the", "core", "of", "his", "problem", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 720, "question": "Do you think it was a mistake to get rid of Paula?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "it", "was", "a", "mistake", "to", "get", "rid", "of", "Paula", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 721, "answer": "Certainly, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Certainly", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110309pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 727, "question": "What do you think of Steven Tyler and J-Lo?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "Steven", "Tyler", "and", "J-Lo", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 728, "answer": "Good.", "answer_tokens": ["Good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steven Tyler"]}}]